Before... you said you wanted
to be friends, but...
My feelings for you...
are not just friendship.
What?
Y-You're right!
Even though we're friends now,
I'm still your mentor.
A superior.
So of course we're not just friends... um...
Senpai, I...
Kamegawa-kun!
We want the birthday people
to do a little closing statement.
Is now a bad time?
No, it's okay.
I'll be right there.
Are you okay, Senpai?
Kannawa-senpai?
Senpai? Hey.
S-Senpai!
Pull yourself together!
I...
Huh?
I need booze.
"I Really Thought About It, Ya Know?!"
Now, that...
sounds like a confession.
B-But he didn't exactly say that it was.
I feel like I can finally say this now.
His feelings for you have
been obvious for ages now.
They have?
Like, "I'm in love with Kannawa-senpai!"
What?!
Kankaiji-senpai and I wished he would
just hurry up and ask you out.
But I think Kamegawa just blurted
that out today on an impulse.
Getting a present from you
got him all excited.
This gift from you makes
me especially happy.
Which is why I think he'll make a
comeback and properly ask you out.
What?
Who knows? Maybe he'll call you right now.
It's a toll-free number.
Are you not happy about this?
Huh?
Being asked out by Kamegawa.
It's not that... I just...
AZUSA KANNAWA-SENPAI
So? Did you ask her out?
No, I didn't...
It's more like I planted the idea of it.
Was it because someone
interrupted in the middle?
No. It was my fault.
Well, I suppose.
You were aiming low by suggesting
being friends in the first place.
Tell me, Kamegawa-kun. What's your type?
M-My type?
I like people like Kannawa.
They make me feel competitive or something.
Competitive?
Kind of like how you want to
climb a wall more the higher it is.
But in the end, I couldn't quite
get along with Kannawa.
What? Really?
Let's go outside for a bit.
Sure.
Looks like it stopped snowing.
Yeah.
It was only recently that Kannawa
started talking normally.
But a certain someone didn't seem
to realize that and got all jealous.
You know how Kannawa doesn't
try to make others like her?
That's why she doesn't bother
getting closer to others.
She doesn't believe that
anyone could ever like her.
Look at all those windows.
Each one is lit up.
Inside them, so many people could be living
wonderful lives that I don't know about.
Since you're under Kannawa's
direct supervision,
there was no way for her
to avoid interacting with you.
It was probably a good thing that you
and Kannawa met as mentor and mentee.
Yeah.
Th-There's still no way to be sure
that was a confession, anyway.
You're still going on about that?
Weren't you happy that
Kamegawa asked you out?
Or is it that...
you don't want to be involved
in an office romance?
Or that you're not exactly against it,
but it's a bit bothersome?
No... I-It's...
I-It's not... bothersome.
Oh?
Wh-What?
Then...
if he were to say what he said to you
to another girl, how would you feel?
I'd hate it...
Senpai!
Tomorrow's our day off!
Let's drink to our hearts' content tonight!
And then we'll have a strategy meeting!
S-Strategy meeting?
To be honest...
I bet you're lacking in
romantic experience, right?
It's hard to believe.
You're super pretty, Senpai.
You'd be so popular.
But that's the good thing about you.
O-Okay...
Which is why I've been thinking.
Uh, yeah?
Instead of going out immediately...
Uh-huh...
I don't feel rested at all.
In the end, Kamegawa never reached out to me.
Not that I'd know what to say if he did...
No!
I've thought this through in my own way!
Whether that was a confession or not...
I'm mentally prepared for either situation!
I'm ready!
Now go!
Good morning.
G...
Gewd myorn... ing...
Later!
Huh? Um...
Can I borrow you for a sec, Kannawa-san?
Of course.
Kannawa-san seems different, don't you think?
Really?
Isn't she always like that?
I think Kamegawa-kun's
the one acting different.
He seems down. I'm worried.
Hey, you three chatterboxes.
Get back to work.
Okay.
Good luck out there.
Stare...
Th-This is awkward.
I think I took too much damage from
failing my first encounter with him.
Um...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What?
Y-Y-Y-Y-You must be worried about
what happened the other day.
I-I'm so sorry.
I said something weird to you
without thinking it through.
You don't need to worry about it right now.
O-Okay.
F-For now!
Um...
I'm going to go buy something to drink.
Something... weird?
Weird?
That was... "weird"?
To Kamegawa, it was weird?
As in, somethin' I don't need to worry about?
I even got advice from Hotta about this...
Over the weekend, I...
really thought about it, ya know!
What am I doing?
Huh?
Huh?!
What do ya mean, "weird"?
What do ya mean, "don't worry"?!
Um, Senpai...
I'm sorry about before.
Um, I also couldn't really...
You...
You said I was special!
That it wasn't just friendship!
You kept sayin' stuff that made no sense!
I lost sleep this weekend 'cuz I couldn't
stop thinkin' 'bout what ya said!
"Don't worry about it"?
Of course I'm gonna worry!
Of course I'll worry about it!
So I...
just kept thinkin' 'bout ya!
I can't even work.
And it's affecting my daily life!
So I wanna do somethin' 'bout this!
Um...
I...
So...
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I've thought it through these last two days!
Yes, ma'am!
Three months!
A three-month trial!
T-Trial?
I'm sayin' that I'll give ya
my time for three months.
What do you think?
You can't pass this up.
What? Um... this conversation
took quite a turn, and...
I can't keep up.
Don't you want it?
I-I do!
All right!
Then it's decided!
Hold on!
Before we talk about that...
I... have something I need to tell y—
Nope!
Huh?!
I've used up my energy for the day!
I'm going home!
Yes, ma'am...
Kannawa-senpai!
I was so moved!
You were actually able to say it!
Yeah. You gave us quite the show.
It was... It was...
It was... completely one-sided...
It's okay!
I'm sure Kamegawa's doing
a little dance right now!
I heard the two of you had a strategy meeting
and decided on the three-month trial?
Y-Yeah.
When we were drinking the other day...
The relationship between the two of you
started as mentor and mentee,
so you skipped through a lot of stuff.
Like going on dates.
Da—
Going out somewhere together,
eating somewhere...
I think you should start by giving those a try!
Give them a try?
In other words, a dating period!
Dating?
It's the trial period to get to know each
other before officially becoming a couple.
Oh, yeah!
That's exactly it!
Th-Then...
is there something I should be doing
during the dating period?
Like, any specific places we should go?
Hmm...
First, you should drop the idea that
there's something specific you need to do.
Huh?
You could end up being
too formal because of that.
Just let things happen naturally.
Wh-What do you mean, "naturally"?
You're already being too
self-conscious, Senpai!
Enjoy your dating period.
Okay.
Remember, Senpai, act natural.
Extra natural!
Y-Yeah!
Which of these did Kamegawa
have the best reaction to?
Oh.
But...
"They all look good," he said.
He complimented me on all of them.
Okay!
I'm so nervous that I ended up
arrivin' super early.
Senpai!
Why're you here?
Huh?
Oh, I mean...
I'm one to talk,
but you're thirty minutes early.
That's too much.
Yeah... I got nervous.
We're just going to eat ramen.
What's there to be nervous about?
B-But isn't this... a date?
I-It's a trial!
A trial date.
Right. It's a trial date.
The tree is so pretty!
Let's take a closer look at it together.
Yeah.
Have you decided on the restaurant?
Oh.
I-I saw on TV a while ago that
there's this good place near here.
I only remember that it's in this area.
Oh, sorry.
I kind of figured this would happen,
so I did some research on my end.
Wh-What do you mean, you "kind of figured"?!
S-Sorry.
So? Where is it?
Oh, um...
A famous place around here would be...
Maybe this one?
Oh! That! That's the one!
It looks good.
I'm so glad.
Thanks, Kamegawa.
You're welcome.
Speaking of ramen, do you...
like...
Yes, I do.
That's good.
Sorry for hitting you.
It's all right.
Okay.
You've got bedhead.
Like, a lot.
What? Where?
Just kiddin'.
Well, you...
Hmm?
Hmm...
You're cute.
Wha—
What made the conversation
take that turn?!
No, uh...
I was going for a comeback,
but I couldn't think of anything
negative about you.
Sorry.
It's rude to say that to your superior.
But...
you're not here with me as my superior today.
W-Well... about that...
You're here to give me three months
of your time... Kannawa-san.
I still don't understand what
you meant when you said
that I was special to you.
I can't even imagine it.
Which is why I want to learn much more
about you over the next three months.
And I want you to learn more about me.
And...
I want to know what that
special thing between us is.
Sure.
I-Is this okay?
Only until we get to the restaurant.
Okay.
L-Let's go!
Which way?
That way.
Oh, that way!
Okay, let's go!
Looks like we can go in shortly.
Yeah.
Do you already know what you're getting?
Nope!
Here's the menu.
Oh, thanks. That helps.
Next in line. Kamegawa-sama!
Yesh!
Oh, wait, that's not me.
Oh, but...
We're Kamegawa.
Come on in.
So good.
It's delicious.
It hits the spot.
Want to try some of mine?
Can I? Thank you.
So? Do you like it?
It's delicious! I can see why it's
a popular spot. Right, Senpai?
Yes. Ah, um...
Let's finish before the noodles get soggy.
Y-You're right.
Let's go to lots more places from now on.
Yeah.